Make sure you hide well.
Let's see if I can catch you.
Move.
Chen Hui actually rigged electric traps.
We'll settle all scores with him later.
There's something wrong with this bottle.
He just wants us dead.
Damn it.
Could something have happened to Sun Bo?
Found it that easily?
Captain Chu.
I found something.
What does a pig feed bag mean?
Anywhere in the city with surveillance,
Chen Hui couldn't possibly hide there.
So the clue
might be in this pig feed bag
and in this photo.
Captain Chu.
I'll have the techs analyze it now.
I just remembered.
This used to be a pig feed factory.
It was supposed to close down,
but debt issues kept it from being demolished.
Yu Tianfang is hiding there.
I'll head over and meet you there now.
The address is...
Okay, I'll come pick you up.
Ma Xiaojun!
Sun Bo!
What happened to Sun Bo?
Captain.
Mission...
accomplished.
Sun Bo!
Chu Feng, where are you going?
Where are you going?
To the feed factory.
To save Tianfang.
I'll drive.
No need.
I know you blame yourself,
but all of this is Chen Hui's doing.
My father once said,
Chen Hui either checkmates,
or gets checkmated.
He's reckless and stubborn.
But we can't let emotions cloud us.
We have to stay rational.
Remember that saying?
Don't always focus on winning.
Watch the steps in front of you first.
This time,
none of us has a way back.
But this game,
we have to win.
Hiding pretty well, kid.
Watch me find you.
You actually got away.
Hello?
Where are you?
He Siqi.
I'll give you a chance.
Yu Tianfang is in my hands.
Want to save his life? Come find me.
Don't move!
I have a feeling Chen Hui
has another scheme up his sleeve.
Besides us and Yu Tianfang,
the one Chen Hui hates most is He Siqi.
I have a bad feeling.
If Chen Hui has already contacted He Siqi,
He Siqi
would probably sneak out.
He Siqi.
For that kid,
you don't even care about your own health.
Is he worth it?
Seeing you like this
breaks my heart.
I'm here.
Let Yu Tianfang go.
I told you to come save Yu Tianfang,
but I never once mentioned
any conditions for releasing him.
Because I never planned to escape from here.
So what do you have to bargain with?
What if I pay money to ransom him?
What money do you have?
My mom left me lots of jewelry.
And every year on my birthday,
she'd give me a small gold bar.
In this case,
the gold bars alone weigh two pounds.
I don't believe you.
The old you would never lie to me.
Everyone is selfish.
No matter how much I loved you,
I had to keep some security for myself.
After all,
the most appealing thing in this world
is money.
Open it up.
I want to see Yu Tianfang first.
What does that kid have that I don't?
You disgust me.
Let's go.
After you.
Siqi.
Tianfang.
Get out of here, now.
Don't worry about me.
Isn't this all because
you want to drag someone down with you?
I'll trade myself for him.
Dying together with you
would be a fitting death, of course.
But
this grudge between the three of us,
how could he not be present?
Millions in jewelry and gold
are right inside this case.
Enough for you to flee.
Let him go.
What if I made you come with me
in exchange for his life?
Siqi.
Don't listen to him.
He's nothing but a cunning old fox.
Don't worry.
I'd rather die than go with him.
Does our past mean nothing to you?
Being so heartless
really breaks my heart.
Women's hearts are the most venomous. Let me guess.
Inside this case of yours,
there might be some hidden trap or weapon.
If I open it, I'll get hurt,
and the two of you can escape.
I'm not as despicable as you.
See?
I didn't lie to you.
Now let him go!
Siqi.
You really underestimate me.
Do you really think
he's the only one I hate?
Siqi.
What a thrill.
You almost set off the gas too early.
This move of yours,
the mask is off.
Fine.
It's my turn to play.
No!
Tianfang!
These genuine, heartfelt tears,
you've never shed any of them for me.
I really wonder
if you ever loved me at all.
Have you been treating me all along
as just a toy to pass the time?
That's right.
I was just playing you.
The one Siqi loves
has always been only me.
You're not even worth a hair on my leg.
Shut up!
Old and ugly,
like a moldy old slab of cured meat.
Even a dog wouldn't touch it.
If I were you,
I'd jump into a septic tank,
to spare society the pollution.
Siqi.
Tianfang!
If you've got the guts,
fight me one-on-one.
Let me go!
Go to hell!
The more you move,
the deeper the poison goes.
Beg me.
Beg me, and I'll give you a couple puffs.
I'd rather die than beg you.
Such backbone.
Then reflect carefully
on the wrongs you've done in this life.
And
what regrets you've left unfulfilled.
The thing I regret most
is ever meeting you.
The biggest mistake
was trusting you.
What I regret most is
not hacking you to death just now.
You're actually a pretty great girl.
But
you didn't give all your love to me.
That's your fault.